quarterpaid.com 2015-06-07

# QuarterPaid - Anti Spam Policy

## Privacy Policy

What we collect and how we use it.

QuarterPaid(http://www.quarterpaid.com) may ask you to provide personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address, telephone number.  
We will not rent, sell or lease this personally identifiable information to other companies or individuals.

This information may be gathered when you visit the Site to:  
Provide feedback in an online survey;  
Request product or service information;  
And / or make purchases.  
When you provide such information to us, we may use it to:  
Deliver requested goods, services or information;  
Provide notices regarding goods or services that you may purchase or be interested in;  
Improve the content and general administration of the Site.  
In connection with a job application or inquiry, whether advertised on this Site or otherwise, you may provide us with a resume or curriculum vitae.  
We may use this information for the purpose of employment consideration or your inquiry. Except where you tell us not to, we will keep the information for future consideration.

Cookies.  
We might use small text files called cookies to improve the overall Site experience.  
Cookies generally do not permit us to personally identify you.  
The use of cookies is now standard operating procedure for most websites.  
You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.  
You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some websites may not work properly.

Links to Third Party Sites.  
This Site may be linked to other web sites on the internet which are not under the control of or maintained by QuarterPaid.  
Such links do not constitute an endorsement by this Site of those other websites, the content displayed therein, or the persons or entities associated therewith.  
QuarterPaid is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of external websites.

Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors.  
QuarterPaid sometimes may offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that is sponsored by or cobranded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. QuarterPaid has no control over the third-party's use of this information.

Security.  
We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

Policy Changes.  
QuarterPaid reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy. Any changes will be made available within this externally posted Privacy Policy.  
We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes as your continued use of the Site will be subject to the then-current privacy policy.
